<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<job-search>
  <jobs total="6109" count="10" start="0">
    <job>
      <id>7394223</id>
      <company>
        <id>1601709</id>
        <name>Fab.com</name>
      </company>
      <job-poster>
        <id>n6dxGXg4We</id>
        <first-name>Renee</first-name>
        <last-name>H.</last-name>
        <headline>Global Director of Talent Acquisition and Cultural Development Fab.com</headline>
      </job-poster>
      <description-snippet>Fab exists for one simple reason: To make you smile! It's more than just a tagline. It's the way we work. Fab is the place to discover the most exciting things for your life. Our modern, urban-inspired products allow everyone to design their lives and express their personal sense of style. Always unique, well-designed, and of the highest quality. At Fab, our employees are just as unique as our pro</description-snippet>
      <location-description>New York, NY</location-description>
    </job>
    <job>
      <id>7403581</id>
      <company>
        <id>8110</id>
        <name>inVentiv Health</name>
      </company>
      <job-poster>
        <id>pvgc1YVaI9</id>
        <first-name>Ryan</first-name>
        <last-name>M.</last-name>
        <headline>Senior Director, Talent Acquisition, inVentiv health</headline>
      </job-poster>
      <description-snippet>Overview inVentiv Health offers best-in-class Clinical, Consulting and Commercial services to global companies seeking to accelerate performance. With 13,000 employees in 40 countries, we rapidly transform promising ideas into commercial reality. inVentiv has committed itself to hiring and retaining the very best talent in the healthcare industry, those who have a single common characteristic: the</description-snippet>
      <location-description>New York- NY [NY]-United States [US]</location-description>
    </job>
    <job>
      <id>9252517</id>
      <company>
        <name>ANN INC.</name>
      </company>
      <job-poster>
        <id>880H5a67Yp</id>
        <first-name>Stephanie</first-name>
        <last-name>B.</last-name>
        <headline>Manager, Talent Resources at ANN INC.</headline>
      </job-poster>
      <description-snippet>Reports To:                 Director, Digital Marketing                         Key Interactions:       Digital Marketing, CRM, Brand Marketing, Creative, Planning, Merchandising     Position Overview: The Email Marketing Manager is responsible for developing and leading LOFT’s advanced email marketing programs.   This is a highly visible and strategic role.  As email is the number one growth chan</description-snippet>
      <location-description>Greater New York City Area</location-description>
    </job>
    <job>
      <id>9252147</id>
      <company>
        <name>ANN INC.</name>
      </company>
      <job-poster>
        <id>880H5a67Yp</id>
        <first-name>Stephanie</first-name>
        <last-name>B.</last-name>
        <headline>Manager, Talent Resources at ANN INC.</headline>
      </job-poster>
      <description-snippet>As a part of the Corporate Strategy function, the Enterprise Initiatives team identifies and executes ANN INC.’s most strategic, complex, and far reaching projects.  In this highly visible and dynamic role, we are seeking the right candidate to work across all functions of the business to drive meaningful long-term growth. The Associate Manager will play an integral role in executing the company’s</description-snippet>
      <location-description>Greater New York City Area</location-description>
    </job>
    <job>
      <id>9231943</id>
      <company>
        <name>ANN INC.</name>
      </company>
      <job-poster>
        <id>880H5a67Yp</id>
        <first-name>Stephanie</first-name>
        <last-name>B.</last-name>
        <headline>Manager, Talent Resources at ANN INC.</headline>
      </job-poster>
      <description-snippet>The Contract Talent Resources Coordinator will support approximately 3- 6 recruiters, director, and other talent resources associates as assigned.  The coordinator will provide support around all scheduling and operational activities, ensuring the success of the talent resources team, while providing an exceptional candidate and hiring manager experience. Coordinator will collaborate with recruite</description-snippet>
      <location-description>Greater New York City Area</location-description>
    </job>
    <job>
      <id>9203462</id>
      <company>
        <name>ANN INC.</name>
      </company>
      <job-poster>
        <id>880H5a67Yp</id>
        <first-name>Stephanie</first-name>
        <last-name>B.</last-name>
        <headline>Manager, Talent Resources at ANN INC.</headline>
      </job-poster>
      <description-snippet>Reports To:               Sr. Director, Marketing Operations, Global Procurement                      As an integral member of the ANN INC. Global Procurement team, this position is responsible for managing ANN INC.’s 3rd party distribution supplier, and all products that go through that 3rd party distribution warehouse to support ANN INC. stores, including packaging, hangers, and other store supp</description-snippet>
      <location-description>Greater New York City Area</location-description>
    </job>
    <job>
      <id>7484794</id>
      <company>
        <name>ANN INC.</name>
      </company>
      <job-poster>
        <id>880H5a67Yp</id>
        <first-name>Stephanie</first-name>
        <last-name>B.</last-name>
        <headline>Manager, Talent Resources at ANN INC.</headline>
      </job-poster>
      <description-snippet>Reporting to the Sr. Director of Marketing Operations, the Marketing Production Manager is responsible for managing the day to day responsibilities for all of the direct mail and instore collateral print production, high –end beauty retouching, and ad production for the LOFT brand. This position will collaborate with the Sr. Director of Marketing Operations on a daily basis in order to ensure proj</description-snippet>
      <location-description>Greater New York City Area</location-description>
    </job>
    <job>
      <id>9162227</id>
      <company>
        <id>946698</id>
        <name>PLANNED PARENTHOOD FEDERATION OF AMERICA</name>
      </company>
      <job-poster>
        <id>jvr1QHW7UA</id>
        <first-name>Karen</first-name>
        <last-name>M.</last-name>
        <headline>Director of Recruitment &amp; Development at Planned Parenthood Federation of America</headline>
      </job-poster>
      <description-snippet>PLANNED PARENTHOOD FEDERATION OF AMERICA  NATIONAL OFFICE - NEW YORK, NEW YORK  Director of Clinical Quality &amp;amp; Operations, CAPS OVERVIEW:For nearly a century, Planned Parenthood Federation of America (PPFA) has fought for a world where every woman has immediate and unfettered access to the basic reproductive care and knowledge that is her human right. With its 71 affiliates managing nearly 800</description-snippet>
      <location-description>NYC - LI - Hudson Valley</location-description>
    </job>
    <job>
      <id>7504901</id>
      <company>
        <id>1089419</id>
        <name>Catchafire</name>
      </company>
      <job-poster>
        <id>UgjJpwQKZB</id>
        <first-name>Vibha</first-name>
        <last-name>C.</last-name>
        <headline>Account Manager at Catchafire</headline>
      </job-poster>
      <description-snippet>Catchafire's mission is to provide talented individuals with meaningful pro bono experiences in order to build capacity for social good organizations. Our partner organization, College and Community Fellowship is looking for help with designing their brand new brochure. They say: Since 2000, College and Community Fellowship (CCF) has provided assistance to over 200 women. These women have earned A</description-snippet>
      <location-description>Greater New York City Area</location-description>
    </job>
    <job>
      <id>7353819</id>
      <company>
        <id>2318133</id>
        <name>Chloe + Isabel Inc.</name>
      </company>
      <job-poster>
        <id>PrsR7PbEKr</id>
        <first-name>Miller</first-name>
        <last-name>C.</last-name>
        <headline>Director of HR and Talent Acquisition at Chloe + Isabel Inc.</headline>
      </job-poster>
      <description-snippet>The Company Founded in 2011, chloe + isabel is a dynamic and socially innovative jewelry brand designed to connect women through a modern-day social-shopping experience. A destination for fashion- loving, creative and confident women, chloe + isabel believes that today’s women deserve jewelry as exceptional as they are! Our independent sales representatives (Merchandisers) offer our products throu</description-snippet>
      <location-description>Greater New York City Area</location-description>
    </job>
  </jobs>
  <num-results>6109</num-results>
  <facets total="1">
    <facet>
      <code>company</code>
      <name>Company</name>
      <buckets total="11">
        <bucket>
          <code>11776</code>
          <name>INC Research</name>
          <count>360</count>
          <selected>false</selected>
        </bucket>
        <bucket>
          <code>76245</code>
          <name>Lovelace Health System</name>
          <count>199</count>
          <selected>false</selected>
        </bucket>
        <bucket>
          <code>2724</code>
          <name>Bombardier Inc.</name>
          <count>174</count>
          <selected>false</selected>
        </bucket>
        <bucket>
          <code>41754</code>
          <name>AccruePartners</name>
          <count>120</count>
          <selected>false</selected>
        </bucket>
        <bucket>
          <code>2614</code>
          <name>Avon</name>
          <count>91</count>
          <selected>false</selected>
        </bucket>
        <bucket>
          <code>166587</code>
          <name>UNC Health Care</name>
          <count>85</count>
          <selected>false</selected>
        </bucket>
        <bucket>
          <code>14406</code>
          <name>We Simplify the Internet (WSI)</name>
          <count>76</count>
          <selected>false</selected>
        </bucket>
        <bucket>
          <code>1835</code>
          <name>Allstate</name>
          <count>73</count>
          <selected>false</selected>
        </bucket>
        <bucket>
          <code>2677</code>
          <name>McDonald's Corporation</name>
          <count>72</count>
          <selected>false</selected>
        </bucket>
        <bucket>
          <code>9479</code>
          <name>First Command Financial Services</name>
          <count>66</count>
          <selected>false</selected>
        </bucket>
        <bucket>
          <code>1714</code>
          <name>Nielsen</name>
          <count>63</count>
          <selected>false</selected>
        </bucket>
      </buckets>
    </facet>
  </facets>
</job-search>